we need to army we need to army
twitchy's we need an army
I need y'all to come in we got something
to do today we got a mission
I don't think this is working
Oh IRL stream yes IRL stream okay all
right we got one person something's kind
of working yo what up
oh yeah look we got people all right
look it's the first stream of 2019
welcome welcome no no no we got we got
yeah look man look a loss happened I'm
just saying a lots happened in my life
you know this is an iPhone eight I don't
got the ax because I don't like the
knotch yo well welcome welcome welcome
remember no talking about coming iron
low gang we'll come get your sub-tab
YouTube absolutely self-defeat oh hi
what up what up
we're are right I'm in LA you guys I'm
in LA and I just want to tell you all 76
I let's get over a hundred and then
we'll start with what we're talking
about guys all right so as you can see
from my beard some girls said that to me
once weird flex but okay and then I
googled it and it was like a thing and
I'm like okay that make sounds kind of
yeah as you can see I've been I've been
I've been wandering the world when are
we gonna stream coding I don't know guys
I look I we got we got 124 people in
here thank you for joining thank you for
joining my my stream I'm here in
beautiful slightly cloudy LA to tell you
guys something and I don't know if I'm
allowed to say this on Twitch but I'm
gonna say it anyway
now well am i homeless sort of sort of
but that's not what we're here to talk
about you guys I want to tell you about
my 2019 dream and my 2019 dream is to be
an Instagram celebrity alright so I'm
sure one of you out there works for
Facebook or knows somebody who works for
Facebook
you guys go out there and I want to be
an Instagram celebrity that's right I
have a dream I want to be in you know
those people with the girls and the cars
and the private jets I'm gonna be an
Instagram celebrity with all the money
that I made from you guys subscribing to
my twitch stream so my Instagram handle
is just George Hotz straight up using my
real name my 20:19 dream is to be an
Instagram celebrity you know I'm gonna
be doing lots of stuff to promote my
personal brand you can watch my
south-by-southwest talk coming up is
called jailbreaking the simulation that
might be kind of fun but go right now go
on your instagrams I know you all have
them and click that click that like and
subscribe button or follow or I don't
know what it is on Instagram but my
Instagram is just George Hotz alright so
also also and I know one of you works
for Facebook out there I need you to get
me verified I need that blue checkmark
the blue checkmark is how you can tell
this is the same cadence that I talked
about for the subscribers how you can
tell who's important and who's not so my
dream in life is to be my dream of 2019
only 2019 is to be a Instagram celebrity
I've been talking about this for a week
now so you know it's a no it's an
important dream I look the hair's gotten
really long you guys the hair's gotten
long it's good it's gotten real long
nope no I've not this isn't a joke you
think I'm joking I'm not joking what I
need you to do is first off follow me on
Instagram and second off if you know
people at Instagram I need you all to
contact them and make sure to get George
Hotz verified if you guys do this I
promise great high-quality content for
you so it's not twitch this year twitch
was last year you all know some common
archive guy went and put all my twitch
streams on YouTube you know we're
getting mad views but
what I've realized is that it's the
future and you need to build a personal
brand and you need to monetize that
personal brand and I want you to all be
here with me on this journey of personal
brand monetization this is my Instagram
at George Hotz you can see the most
recent one is a picture I mean I don't
really know much about Instagram I do
know it's a facebook property and you
all know how I feel about Facebook but
I've also heard that that people get
lots of money for sponsored posts on
Instagram sponsored posts on Instagram
so if you guys want to see that become a
reality if you guys want to see the geo
hot keyboard brand you know we're gonna
make some branded keyboards what do you
think Brandon keyboards I know you were
always asking about the keyboard um no
streaming programming was 2019 shaving
programming was 2018 it's 2019 and my
new dream is to be an Instagram
celebrity what we're gonna make lots of
money and it's gonna be like you're on
this journey with me
except you know I get the money but if
still you'll get to see the money and I
read a study once that showed that that
was very similar no I tried playing for
at night I was pretty bad at it but
yo-yo it has been a long time it has
been a long time so if you guys have any
questions I should get a dog I thought
about buying a house
unemployed give me a job I don't know
who's giving you a job man look look at
my beard do I look like I have jobs to
give people but if I do become an
Instagram influencers celebrity you know
Instagram celebrity I'll hire like
editors and you know people to follow me
around and bodyguards and whatever
whatever all those doesn't it sound fun
no but yeah get geo verified exactly I'm
verified on Twitter but guys I have a
you know I used to be addicted to
Twitter so I can't tweet you know I
might relapse and go back on Twitter um
yeah you missed the Skokie's uh you
weren't calming eyes discord yeah I am
y'all are discord now you should buy a
semi-truck you could live in it I
thought about buying a station wagon and
living in it um yeah yeah to help my
Instagram get verified I linked to my
Wikipedia but I used to link to my
soundcloud we're gonna personal brand
you know everyone needs a personal brand
these days right like there's two things
you can do about the future right you
can either be upset or follow the
Microsoft pattern of embrace extend
extinguish right and that's what we're
going with your embrace extend
extinguish and we're on step one of that
right now we're on the embrace side of
things so yo you guys go follow me on
instagram at george hotz it's just my
name no no no no I'm not this isn't
common AI related this is a personal
George Hotz property the car may i sir
properties of course property of comma
AI you know social is a brand these days
guys got a thank you Pharisee though I
don't know who Terry Davis's who is that
but yeah guys you should stop smoking
pot I mean that's that's the option I
want to get with the times I don't want
to be one of those left behind integrate
the internet celebrities like iJustine
who's Terry Davis
is that someone cool says someone I
should know I kind of know things like
that if I want to be Instagram famous I
know as I'm telling I was hanging out I
think it was last weekend two weekends
ago now is hanging out and I was like
I'm gonna be an Instagram celebrity in
2019 you guys watch you missed the old
geo ha you know what some people miss
the old Drake and I miss the old Drake
too before you had a kid that's right Oh
Temple OS yeah ya know we were just
talking about temple of us build
automated farming equipment is this my
hippie face you guys can call it
whatever you want but all I'm saying is
go right now follow me on instagram
george hotz and get me verified so if
any you work for facebook or know
somebody who works for facebook i really
appreciate it
no i don't know man I don't know but
I'll see you all later
I got things to do absolutely I do the
Joe Rogan podcast absolutely you could
do what you're doing on Twitter no I
don't tweet man I got a Twitter but you
launder the putt yeah Ilana you want you
know calming I exist man calming I exist
they have some crazy announcements
coming up too but I'm here and if you
guys want to see what comes next at door
tots on Instagram
I'll see you all later but bye bye bye
bye bye bye Twiggy's
I don't know how to end these things oh
ya know if you guys get me oh no I will
do will do two more questions we got any
more questions got any more questions I
can't figure out Adams I can't figure
out and I don't know how to click the
button hi bye love ya Joe Rogan that'd
be sick guys um no I don't know the
future is gonna be an interesting place
my Instagram is at your charts am i
trespassing at someone's house don't
don't tell anybody
um no but uh you gotta ask this question
and this is the only question that's
gonna be relevant in the future its
where do you want to be when the
singularity plays out all right
I think if I swipe down down I swipe ya
the Instagram Instagram source that all
right bye-bye
down